<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fluxus 2014</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="summary">Fluxus is the annual college festival of IIT Indore. Its an exceptional confluence of exquisite cultural displays with technological innovations reverberating in an aura filled with excitement, amusement and splendor. After the overwhelming success of Fluxus 2013, IIT Indore is back with Fluxus 2014 which promises to transcend all the thresholds of science and entertainment.\nFluxus 2014 guarantees inimitable world, teeming with boundless merriment, talent and skill as you plunge into the ocean of entertainment at this three day youth extravaganza. This edition of Fluxus, for the first time since its birth, incorporates the theme of "The Desi Carnival" boasting of unique and exciting events and performances ranging from Competitions to Concerts, from Workshops to Guest Lectures and from Literary Arts to Model United Nations.\n\nA roller-coaster of emotions in the Drama competition to an ideal treasure-hunt spread throughout the city, you get it all here at FLUXUS\'14. In a nutshell, the three day extravaganza at Fluxus will be a showcase of spectacular talent and an exhilarating experience for the populace. We have something for everyone - be it a sports lover, a music fanatic, a dance freak, a quiz wizard or simply a fun loving mortal. Fuelling the fire of passion, inquisitiveness and the desire for perfection with a topping of unique and challenging events ingeniously crafted by some of the smartest young minds of India. Feel the fire consume your soul as you compete against the best teams of the country!\n\nPro-shows are here to enliven the nights!!! Replete with nerve-racking entertainment, these shows are sure to set your senses on fire. From music to dance to stunts these pros are guaranteed dynamites of action packed entertainment. So wear your dancing shoes, clear your throat and bang your heads to the tantalizing tunes of our pro-entertainers. We promise you to be entertained to your bones..\nThree fun filled nights of Fashion, Dance and Concerts..\n\n\n\nIts not just a festival, its a celebration.</string>

    <array id="eventTypesIdArr" name="eventTypesIdArr">
        <item>@array/proEvents</item>
        <item>@array/cultEvents</item>
        <item>@array/techEvents</item>
        <item>@array/maraEvents</item>
        <item>@array/workshops</item>
        <item>@array/quizEvents</item>
        <item>@array/litEvents</item>
    </array>
    <array id="eventAbstIdArr" name="eventAbstIdArr">
        <item>@array/proEventsAbst</item>
        <item>@array/cultEventsAbst</item>
        <item>@array/techEventsAbst</item>
        <item>@array/maraEventsAbst</item>
        <item>@array/workshopsAbst</item>
        <item>@array/quizEventsAbst</item>
        <item>@array/litEventsAbst</item>
    </array>

    <string-array id="eventTypes" name="eventTypes">
        <item>Pro-Shows</item>
        <item>Performing Arts</item>
        <item>Tech Theatre</item>
        <item>Marathon</item>
        <item>Workshops</item>
        <item>Quiz Fest</item>
        <item>Literary Fest</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="proEvents" name="proEvents">
        <item>Popular Nite</item>
        <item>Performance Nite</item>
        <item>Elegencia</item>
        <item>Stunt Mania</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="cultEvents" name="cultEvents">
		<item>Dance Prix</item>
		<item>Dramatics</item>
		<item>Kreatrix</item>
		<item>Painting Competition</item>
		<item>Shutter Bug</item>
		<item>Treasure Raider</item>
		<item>Voice of fluxus</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="techEvents" name="techEvents">
        <item>Android Application Development Challenge</item>
		<item>Aqua Robotics</item>
		<item>Bheja Fry</item>
		<item>CID Calculator</item>
		<item>Divide By Zero</item>
		<item>Enigma</item>
		<item>Eye Bot Soccer</item>
		<item>License to Kill</item>
		<item>Monster Wheels</item>
		<item>RoboOne</item>
		<item>Struttura</item>
		<item>Tail Spin</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="maraEvents" name="maraEvents">
        <item>Go Green</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="workshops" name="workshops">
        <item>ArduinoBOTics</item>
		<item>ARM Microcontrollers</item>
		<item>AutoSpark</item>
		<item>Ethical Hacking</item>
        <item>Mobile Hacking and Penetration Testing</item>
        <item>Automotive System and Development</item>
		<item>Android Application Development Challenge</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="quizEvents" name="quizEvents">
        <item>Introduction</item>
        <item>Obscura</item>
        <item>Eureka!</item>
        <item>Collosseum</item>
        <item>Quizooka</item>
        <item>Technophilia</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="litEvents" name="litEvents">
		<item>PotterMania</item>
		<item>Un\-Srcamlbe</item>
		<item>Cache of the Lexis</item>
		<item>Ransense</item>
        <item>JAM</item>
		<item>Spell Bee</item>
		<item>Wordwars</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array id="proEventsAbst" name="proEventsAbst">
		<item>Music expresses which cannot be said and on which it is impossible to be silent. So come dive into the sea of fun at the most awaited Night of the whole festival.. This Night is all about fame and Music. Fluxus \'14 brings you the popular artist of our Bollywood Genre, raising your adrenaline levels to the peaks. Clear your throats, tie your shoes.. Get ready to JUMP as high as you can and SHOUT your throats out..\n\n\nArtist yet to be disclosed..</item>
		<item>Music give soul to the universe, wings to the imagination, flight to your soul and life to everything. Fluxus@14 brings you one of the most popular Rock Bands on the Penultimate Night of the Festival. So, all the guys and girls in the crowd let your hair loose and head-bang to the rhythm of the beats as the music builds you up to a crescendo of fun and joy.\n\nBand yet to be disclosed..</item>
		<item>Fashion is architecture, it is a matter of flawless proportions. For the first time in the history of Fluxus festival, we organize a fashion show, Elegencia. Because for us, collegians, every day is a Fashion show.. this world is our runway. It’s not every night that you experience the joy of being face to face with true professionals, being enthralled by their moves and being amazed by their innovative and beautiful wardrobe. So, join us at Fluxus as we watch, with bated breaths, the glamour unfold on stage.</item>
		<item>Everyone can ride a bike, but only some can perfect the skill of bike-riding enough to put up a show. At the glorious festival Fluxus’14 we bring a group of these perfectionists to make your eyes pop and your jaws drop. Featuring in Stunt Mania 2.0, they are fast, they are quick… only to make sure you don’t blink even for a millisecond.</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array id="cultEventsAbst" name="cultEventsAbst">
      <item>\"Dance is the hidden language of the soul\"\- Martha Graham.\nDance Prix the dance competition of Fluxus gives a stage to the Indian youth to showcase their energy and moves.\nIt is the most awaited competitions of the festival which attracts a lot of participation and a huge crowd. The competition is divided into two categories:\-\n1.Solonyye Tantsy\-free style solo dancing.\n2.Western Gruppa Tantsy\-western group dance.\n\nFree style solo dancing\nSolonyye Tantsy\n\nRules\-\n1. The event has a multiple rounds. The winners will be declared after the end of the final round.\n2. Time limit\- (2+1) minutes\n3. Participants should come prepared with their own tracks.\n4. Participants may use more than one song in their performance.\n5. No props are allowed.\n6. Five participants will be shortlisted.\n\nFinals: \n1. Time limit: (3) minutes.\n2. Impromptu dancing\-tracks will be provided after the elimination round (prelims) to the selected participants.\n3. Participants are not allowed to use props as a part of their performance.\n4. In case of conflicts, decision of the judges would be considered final.\n5. Judging Criteria: Choreography, Energy, Synchronization, Stage utilization, Costumes, Overall impact.\n\nWestern group dance\-\"WesternGruppaTantsy\" \n(Any western dance form e.g hip hop,jazz,street dance)\n\nRules\-\n1. The event has a single round. The winners will be declared after the end of this round.\n2. Time limit \- (5+5) minutes\n3. Teams will come prepared with their tracks.\n4. Team size\- minimum 4, no maximum limit.\n5. Props: will have to be arranged by the participants themselves. A prop is anything which is not worn on the body as a part of the costume, such as a hand\-held hat, stick, ball, chair, or any piece of costume that is removed during the routine. Equipment which require electricity or that which we consider hazardous (such as fire, smoke, fog devices, knives, throwing of confetti or glitter, etc.) are not allowed.\n6. Live music not allowed.\n7. Teams should bring music or songs that they want to use for their performance in a pen drive.\n8. Teams may use more than one song in their performance.\n9. Teams must follow the time limits. Teams shall be penalized by judges for not doing so.\n10. Judging Criteria:Choreography, Energy, Synchronization, Stage utilization, Costumes, Overall impact.\n\nDates : Yet to be released\n\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nJuniper Gujral: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nShweta Katheria: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
      <item>Akaash Vani of DRAMATICS\-For PLAYers.\nDrama is theater, life, an escape from life, happiness, and sadness all rolled into one. It was once thought that drama was when actors cried. But drama is when the audience cries.Dramatics event of Fluxus 2014 brings an opportunity to all those \'Himmatwale\' who truly believe in it and think that they can actually be the \'Lootera\' of the audience\'s hearts. So gear up since the time to act is now! Somebody go get the Director.\nBHAAG MILKA BHAAG..\n\n For all Sub\-events.\n\n1. No props other than chairs and tables will be arranged (that too on prior mention).However participants can get their own props if required.\n2. Mode of language can be English, Hindi or \"English Vinglish\" (bilingual).\n3. No \"Dirty Picture\": vulgarity or indecency is not allowed.\n4. Decision given by the judges will be \"full and final\".\n5. A computer/laptop for background music will be provided. Please bring the music in CDs in MP3 format and not in audio cassettes .You can also perform live music but the necessary instruments must be arranged by the team.\n6. Nothing will be provided for prior practice.\n7. Participants are allowed to take part in more than one event of Dramatics.\n8. Participants must make sure that their act doesnt offend anyones religious sentiments or feelings.\n9. Participants can perform their acts for time less than the maximum time also.\n\nLightening of candles, matches or inflammable substances, spilling of any fluids is not allowed and will result in disqualification.\n\nGOLMAAL:\nGolmaal expects a continuous story with \'bhelpuri\'  of celebs and characters ,kuch khatte kuch meethe  from any field can take a new avataar in your story.Let your imagination run wild:For example Auro kidnaps Jayakant Shikare to forcefully marry his relative Sheila and Bodyguard Khali goes to his rescue in a fighter plane gifted by Osama.\n\nSpecifications for golmaal:\nMinimum number of participants is 4.\nMaximum number of microphones provided is 6. \nGolmaal consists of two levels:\n1.Jhalak Dikhla Jaa (The Elimination Round): Elimination round has a maximum time limit of 2\-3min in which the group is expected to present a trailer of their act.\nThose who pass the elimination round will have to give the final round.\n 2. Aa Dekhe Jara (The Final Round): Final round has a time limit of 15\-20 min.\n\nANDAAZ APNA APNA  \n\nAndaaz apna apna(A3) is a platform for \'Khiladis\'. The stage is waiting for \'The one (wo)man army\' to amuse the audience with their mimicry, standup comedy, ventriloquism.In short it is a solo performance by the young blood.\n\nSpecifications for Andaaz Apna Apna:\n1. Maximum time limit is 15 min.\n2. The time specified is from empty stage to empty stage so be \"Tezz\"(fast).\n\nDates : Yet to be released\n\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nM.Srilakshmi: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
      <item>Hey Dramebaazon, the time has come. Gather your folks, transform your ingeniously written scripts into film, sparkled up with the forte of actors guided by apt direction. If you think you, your actors, and your camera can weave magic on 35mm, then FLUXUS is your stage! Reach out to the common man. Win hearts and spark a revolution. Be creatively filmy..\n\n1. The submitted video should fit within the categories of mini\-documentary, mini\-drama or fiction and be a cohesive short video. Commercials, music videos or works that are part of a larger project are not eligible.\n2. There is no entry fee.\n3. Number of participants in each group must not exceed 10.\n4. Actors within the production may be any age.\n5. There are 2 forms, Registration form and Submission form. Once the team has registered, they can submit their movie anytime before 25th January 2014.\n6. The Group must have their own Gmail ID as the movie needs to be shared on Google Drive at the time of submission.\n7. It is the responsibility of the group to ensure that the movie submitted meets all the requirements specified in the doc.\n8. No videos that are \"objectionable\" will be considered. According to law, a video is rated objectionable if it \"describes, depicts, expresses, or otherwise deals with matters such as sex, horror, crime cruelty, or violence in such a manner that the availability of the publication is likely to be injurious to the public good\".\n9. If you enter more than one video, you must fill out separate submission forms for each video. Schools or colleges can submit as many entries as they wish, as long as each is a complete stand\-alone work.\n10. You must not copy or download any video from internet.\n11. The theme of the video is up to the Group participating.\n\n\n Rules for Submission:\n\n1. Video format: mp4, MPEG, WMV or mov format.\n2. Time limit: 5 to 15 minutes.\n3. The movie must be in English or Hindi or must have English or Hindi subtitles.\n\nAwards and Judging Criteria\n1. First round selection (Semi\-final round):  The top 10 entries will be selected by our judge\'s panel. These entries will be uploaded on our Youtube Channel\n2. Second round selection (Finals): \na) Public choice award:  The movie with the maximum likes on Official YouTube channel of Fluxus will be the winner.\nb) Critics award: The judges will select one movie from the winner entries of the semi\-final round.\n\n Important Dates\n\n1. Registration: Ends by January 25th.\n2. Declaration of First round results: 10 days before Fluxus starts (Dates to be released).\n3. Declaration of final round winners: Fluxus pro show (Dates to be released).\n\n How to Register?  \nFollow the below given steps in order to register yourself for Kreatrix:\n1. Fill out the form. (Click here)  Only details of the group leader are required. All the participants need not register at this step. \n2. You will be sent a confirmation e\-mail on your Gmail ID within 24 hours (this will be considered as your Group Gmail ID)\n3. The confirmation e\-mail implies successful registration.\n4. The registered group can submit the movie anytime before 25th January 2014.\n\n How to Submit the movie? \nFollow the below given steps in order to submit your movie:\n1. Make sure that one member of the group i.e. the group leader has registered. If not, follow the steps given under \"How to Register?\" section.\n2. Prepare a short description of your movie.\n3. Fill out this form(Click here) Details of all the participants must be filled in this form.\n4. Upload your movie on your Google Drive (through your Group Gmail ID)5. Share the movie on Google Drive with xxx@xmail.com\n6. If you\'ve followed all the steps, you\'ll receive a confirmation email within 24 hours and your movie will be successfully submitted.\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nAayushi Malviya: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nDiksha Golait: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
      <item>As they say \'Art is Music to the eyes\' So all the artists out there, come up to the \'phata canvas nikla painter\', at Fluxus\'14, identify your tune, put a clourful rythm to it, add some lyrical strokes and present to us your song on our canvas.\n\n \nA standard size chart sheet, canvas like, six basic colors and three different size brushes will be given.\n1.Participants can use extra materials of their own other than the given ones.\n2.An image or picture of the art to be made can be used will making the painting.\n3.Registration can be done online or on spot.\n4.The painting can be made in anytime on first and second day of the fest at the given place.\n\nJudging Criteria\n The painting work will be judged on the basis of \n I. Creativity \n       II. Painting Skills\n       III. Neatness\n\nAttraction Keys\n All the paintings will be exhibited on the third day of the fest. If your painting attracts any buyer, you`ll be getting half the worth of your painting.\n The best painter of the show will get a chance to meet the Pro\-show artist personally and gift his/her art to the artist.\n\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nNamit Agarwal: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nRahul Mehlawat: Email: ee1200229@iiti.ac.in Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
      <item>\'Taking pictures is savoring life intensely every hundredth of a second\' \-Mark Rimbaud\nPhotography is a way of captivating the moments of life as they gaze at you star\-struck and bewitched\-forever at your service. What you have caught on film is captured forever. It remembers little things, long after you have forgotten everything. Fluxus invites you to showcase your caliber and passion in this genre of art and compete with some of the best photographers in the country.\nShutter Bug, the official photography competition organizer for Fluxus conducts three parallel events:\n1. There will be a fortnightly competition in which themes will be given at regular intervals. Winning photographers will be awarded handsomely.\n2. The group event will examine photographs submitted by different photography clubs.\n3. There will be a non\-professional level uploading\-liking photography competition without any theme. The photographs will have a \'Fluxus\'14 IIT Indore\' watermark and one with maximum likes will win.\n\n\n1. Photograph must be in digital format.\n2. All photographs must have a title or a tagline.\n3. Only online entries will be eligible. No print or film submissions will be accepted for entry in the contest.\n4. All digital files must be at least 1,000 pixels wide (for horizontal image) or 1,000 pixels tall (for vertical image).\n5. All entries must have a resolution of 5 million pixels or greater (5 megapixels)\n6.Only minor color correction or brightness adjustments are acceptable, as is cropping. High Dynamics Range Images (HDR) and stitched panoramas are not acceptable.\n7. Watermarks are not acceptable unless otherwise specified.\n8. The entries in each category will be judged separately, in accordance with the judging criteria. \n9. IIT Indore reserves the right to examine the original photograph/ source material in order to confirm compliance with these rules.\n10. Entries are to be sent as a .zip/.rar file containing all the photos and the optional .pdf \n\nDates: Yet to be released\n\n\n For Details, Contact:\nKanza Naeem: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nTrupti Saundar: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
      <item>Ever fantasized about a world full of treasures and mystery where adventurousness and curiosity rule and reflex and acumen makes you the front runner? If you envision yourself being a raider of riches, a seeker of secrets, then here is your chance.  Let your wits go wild and plunge into the ocean of unknown thrills. Break bounds and brainstorm to reveal what is behind the veil.\n\n Structure of the Event\nThe event starts with a written test. The test should be given in a groups of two.\n1. The results will be disclosed after a half an hour and 10 top teams will be qualifying for the Next round.\n2. The selected 10 teams will be participating in the Treasure Hunt which spreads across the complete city. One clue leading to the other, and the last clue leading to the prize.\n 3. And the top 3 teams will be given Exciting prizes.\n 4. Participation Certificates will be given to every qualified member.\n\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nMadhulika Deshmukh: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nNeha Kataria: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
      <item>After silence what comes nearest to expressing the inexpressible is MUSIC!! \nMusic speaks what cannot be expressed, soothes the mind and give it rest, heals the heart and makes it whole, flows from heaven to the soul. So all the music lovers get set to fall in love with music and to witness rivalry, companionship and enjoyment in a whole new dimension with VOICE OF FLUXUS.\nWith profoundly high watts of sound and truly captivating performances this celebration of Indian music should not be missed by any music enthusiast.\n\n\nThis is a solo singing competition. In which participants have to bring their own Karaoke or instrumental for their performances. All songs being performed should belong to be in Hindi. Not Dubbed to Hindi.\n\nThe event has 3 rounds, the prelims, Sing Along, the semifinals, Choose and Sing, and the finals, Can you duet? All the three are Elimination rounds.The structure of the respective rounds are as follows, \n\nSing Along\n\n• Participants have to bring their own Karaoke or instrumental for their performances. All songs being performed should belong to be in Hindi. Not Dubbed to Hindi.\n• The performance should last to 2\-4 minutes.\n• 20% of the contestants will be qualified for the Next Round.\n\nChoose and sing\n\n• A List of songs will be provided, of which the semi\-finalist will pick one song.\n• 30 minutes will be provided for preparation!\n• The chosen song will be provided for the preparation by the organizers.\n• Karaoke and written lyrics will be provided do individually.\n• 2 of the semi\-finalists will be qualified for the next round.\n\nCan u duet?\n\n• 2 different songs will be given on spot and both the finalists have to sing them as duet. (Karaoke and written lyrics will be provided)\n• 30 min for preparation!\n• Pre\- recorded song will be provided for the preparation by the organizers.\nOne final winner will be declared.\n\n\n For Details, Contact:\nSushmita:Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nAditi: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nIshrat:Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
   </string-array>
	<string-array id="techEventsAbst" name="techEventsAbst">
	    <item>It is time to hone your app development skills Fluxus 2014 presents you the Android App Development Challenge, a platform to test your app development skills against competition from across India. All you have to do is develop a simple app based on the problem statement provided by us, and submit it. The problem statement will be released on 4th January and the deadline for submission is 30th January. We will announce the results of this round by 3rd February, and the top 6 contestants from this round will get a chance to compete in the final rounds, which will be held during Fluxus 2014. These 6 winners will also get a chance to attend 1-day FREE Advanced Workshop on Android. Exciting prizes, worth Rs. 1 Lakh, and cool Google goodies to be given out in the final round.\n\n  Problem Statment \n\n Event Dates: 4th January 2014 to 30th January 2014 \nRegistration Link:http://goo.gl/12fiYt\nFor details, Contact :\nAravind Sagar : Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nV Priyan : Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nKishore Rajendra Email: xxx@xmail.com  Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>As a kid have you ever played with paper boat..? Have you ever fancied yourself as a pirate.? Time has come now to leave all this kid thing and prove your mettle. FLUXUS gives you unique opportunity to prove yourself. So brace yourself for an interminable voyage. Get ready to wash away your opponents.Prizes worth Rs. 20,000 at stake!\n\n  Problem Statement\n\n Event Dates: During Fluxus \nFor details, Contact:\nChitti Sandeep Teja: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nHemang Desai: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>If knowledge excites you, if you like to tickle your grey cells by asking and answering questions, If you want to enjoy the thrill of cracking a well framed question, Then Bheja Fry is the place to be.. We, at Fluxus have a plethora of quizzes to grill you: From Technophilia, the IT Quiz to Obscura, the IQ Quiz; from How Stuff Works, the Science Quiz to the Sports and Entertainment Quiz.So, if you are just lurking around the corner, come and give it a try..\n\nEvent Dates: During Fluxus 2014</item>
		<item>\"He who refuses to do arithmetic is doomed to talk nonsense\" - John McCarthy \n\nSince time immemorial, mankind has used numbers to assist him in counting. He counted with fingers, stones, phases of the moon.. and later on with abacus and now with calculators. As time changes, we get accurate results in a short span of time. Fluxus provides you to create this advances in arithmetic system, in return to bag exciting prizes. C.I.D calculator, the event to test your skills in electronics and programming as well, let us see whose product is accurate.\n\n  Event Dates: During Fluxus 2014\n\nPrizes worth Rs. 10,000 at stake \n\n   Data Sheet\n  Problem Statement\n\n For details, Contact :\nP.Venkata Sai Vamsi: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>\"Talk is cheap. Show me the code.\" - Linus Torvalds\n\n The world around us is coded. From games to gadgets, from websites to mobile applications, from tiny microprocessors to huge missiles, and from Hello World to  Computer Visualization, Programming has voyaged a lot. Fluxus 2014 brings a prospect to ascertain your coding skills, major your logistics and express your Creativity. So Fellow Chefs, come on the Board, take out the Sword and CODE ON!!!\n\nEvent Dates: First week of February, 2014 (Will be updated soon) \nFor details, Contact:\nDarshil Babel: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nMohit Goyal: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>Have you ever fancied about stepping into the shoes of an explorer and searching for some hidden treasures?Enigma allows you to experience the thrill from the comfort of your room with our online treasure hunt.Look for clues; take help from every scam, hustle, trickery, flimflam and stratagem and bamboozle whosoever you can think of to reach the final destination and win the prize. The answers or clues can be hidden anywhere on the Internet. Players use clues and hints given along with the question to get the answer.Enigma provides you with a very good learning opportunity, enabling you to explore new areas you might be unaware of.The contest is for all age groups, no prior knowledge except using google, is required.So join us in a week of cracking, mysterious and enigmatic experience.Win attractive Fluxus Goodies as Prizes..!!!!\n\nFor details, Contact:\nAbhinav Jain: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nMohit Goyal: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nYadnesh Patil: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>The next generation of robots with vision - eye bots are ready to set ablaze the field of robo-soccer. On an uninhabited alien planet the eye bots will face off one another and will send live vision to their controllers on earth. Millions of light years away humans will control their bots in a challenging soccer match. It is time for robo enthusiasts to accept this challenge and test their metal hounds in a unique and perilous fight.\n\n   Problem Statement \n\n  Event Dates: During Fluxus, 2014 (Will be updated soon) \n For details, Contact:\nEshan Yash Sharma: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nIshan Patil  :Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>The Queen at the Buckingham Palace is in grave danger! Only Agent 007 can save Her Majesty. Meanwhile MI6 sends a signal, having all the information about the conspiracy, which is processed at specific locations across the world. Only YOU can design the appropriate circuit for Bond to save the day. \n\n  Problem Statement\n\n Event Dates: During Fluxus\'14 \n For details, Contact:\nHina Arora: Email: xxx@xmail.com\nMounika Reddy Maddhula: xxx@xmail.com\nAshwini Muthineni: xxx@xmail.com.com</item>
		<item>\"Do not go where the path may lead; go instead where there is no path and leave a trail\"-Ralph Waldo Emerson\n\nFor some, Off-Roading is a form of Freedom. The Freedom to Go Anywhere and Do Anything. Are you one of those OffRoad Fanatics? Fluxus 2014 offers you an Opportunity to give vent to your Desire. Develop a RC vehicle that handles any challenge the tricky terrian has to offer.So Gear-Up to leave your Opponents in Dust.. \n\n  Problem Statement\n\n Event Dates: During Fluxus 2014\n\nRegistration Fees: Rs. 200 per team \n\n\n\nFor details, Contact:\nPratik Bagal: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nPratik Juikar: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>\"It is hard to follow one great vision in this world of darkness and of many changing shadows. Among those men get lost.\" In our journey of life to reach our destiny we have to follow some really challenging paths, and often the paths followed in reaching our goals is more enticing than the goal itself!! Flabbergast the audience and organizers of FLUXUS by designing an agile and creative line following bot that can make its way through any hics and hurdles coming in its path to reach the glory in least time possible.\n\n   Problem Statement\n\n Event Dates: During Fluxus 2014\nRegistration Fees: Rs. 200/- per team\nFor details, Contact:\nSuyash Bhangale: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nAshish Jatav: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>\"Strive for perfection in everything you do. Take the best that exists and make it better. When it does not exist, design it.\" -Sir Henry Royce \nSince time immemorial, human beings have been engaged in building all kind of edifices. From huts made of mud to Taj Mahal we have definitely came a long way. In the modern times the moment we look around us we find ourselves surrounded by many fascinating structures whether to be flyover, skyscraper or a dam.Fluxus bring you the challenge to design a structure with your own techniques and ideas to prove your mettle as a successful engineer. \n\n  Problem Statement \n\n Event Dates: During Fluxus \n For details, Contact:\nSarthak Jagetiya: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>\"If you were born without wings, do nothing to prevent them from growing.\" -Coco Chanel\n Even before Wright Brothers, George Cayley, sometimes referred to as the Father of Aerodynamics designed his first successful glider to carry a human aloft in 1853 after identifying the various forces acting on an aircraft. Let us just get back in time with our balsas to experience the same joy and excitement and to rule our future. So, we invite you to be a part of this exciting event , which we promise will be a visual treat \n\n   Problem Statement \n\n  Event Dates: During Fluxus, 2014 \n For details, Contact:\nDavid Gudapati: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nPrasad Kulkarni: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nKarthik Marneni: Email: xxx@xmail.com Mob: +91 xxxxxxxxxx</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array id="maraEventsAbst" name="maraEventsAbst">
		<item>Long distant sprint for the most burning topic of this decade - "GO GREEN"! CITY MARATHON It is a marathon run not for a few miles, not for a few hours, but for a noble cause that you really believe in solving, a cause that needs everyone’s attention.</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array id="workshopsAbst" name="workshopsAbst">
		<item>ArduinoBOTics is a workshop that very interestingly introduces you to the exciting world of Embedded  Systems. It is a combination of Mechanical Designing\-Electronics Control \-Programming Intelligence. Arduino is an open\-source electronics prototyping platform based on flexible, easy\-to\-use hardware and software. This training of two days is aimed at giving hands\-on feel of working with industry adopted microcontrollers. Various interesting open problems are floated and the participants are encouraged to think out\-of\-box and come up with innovative ideas. It is intended for artists, designers, hobbyists, and anyone interested in creating interactive objects or environments.\n\nThe fee is Rs. 1200\/\- for each student\n\nTakeaway\n1. Kit worth Rs. 5000\/\- in a team of 5 students.\n2. Certificate of participation will also be given to each participant.\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nVinit Sharaswat+91\-xxxxxxxxxx    xxx@xmail.com\nVineet Kataria+91\-xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>ARM Microcontrollers, the latest in controllers family is in high demand within industries. These 32 bit chip is too far better than old controller architectures. The workshop on \"ADVANCE EMBEDDED SYSTEM USING ARM MICROCONTROLLERS\" will be a two full day exhaustive workshop and will cover detailed theory and practical sessions, with hands\-on experience for the students to learn a 32 bit ARM Microcontroller with advance Raspberry Pi kit.During the workshop, the students learn how to sense and control the physical world using computer programs running on 32 bit controllers. These high speed controllers are brought in easy process to make students capable to use ARM family controllers. The workshop is aimed to work on RASPBERRY PI boards and learn various interfacings.\n\nThe fee is Rs. 790\/\- per student.\n\nTakeaway\n1.Participation Certificate will be given to all participants.\n2. Participants will be provided an exhaustive handbook which will contain all covered topics, codes and kits description.\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nShubanshu Bajaj +91\-xxxxxxxxxx xxx@xmail.com\nShikhar Bansa+91\-xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>A two Day Workshop (8 hours per day) on  AutoSpark (Workshop on Automobile Mechanics and IC Engine Design.) is presented. The Workshop includes exhaustive learning sessions with comprehensive theory and practical hands on, providing advanced learning which includes Basics of designing software i.e. CATIA V5 or Solidworks and learning of whole Automobile unit live Engine and car (if possible) through demonstration.The workshop is highly beneficial for students who wish to pursue a career in Automobile Industry.\n\nThe fee is Rs. 1000\/\- per student.\n\nTakeaway\n1. Participation Certificates will be given to all the participants\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nShantanu Rajput  +91\-xxxxxxxxxx xxx@xmail.com\nVikas Sankhla+91\-xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>The September 9\/11 Attacks on the World Trade Center ignited a very important question in the hearts of the founders of EC\-Council. Shortly after the attacks, they researched the web for \"Information Security\" programs that would be able to provide Information Security professionals with the necessary tools and education that will help them avert a cyber war, should the need ever arise. The results returned from the research were disappointing and that motivated them to form the International Council of Electronic Commerce Consultants, known as the EC\-Council. They soon gained the support of subject matter experts from all over the world that eventually led to the creation of various standards and certifications both in the electronic commerce and information security space.The EC\-Council is known primarily as a professional certification body. Its best\-known certification is the Certified Ethical Hacker. Now, EC council presents a two day (8 hours/day) workshop on Ethical Hacking. The participants will be benefitted through Demonstrations of  Latest Hacking Techniques and Tools and PowerPoint Presentations, Live Demos and Hacking Tutorials with HD Videos. Also, they will learn and interact with EC Council Certified Industry Experts.\n\nThe fee is Rs. 1000\/\- per student.\n\nTakeaway\n1.Toolkit (Hacking Tools + Backtrack) will be provided to each participant.\n2. Participation Certificates will be given to all the participants\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nRadhe+91\-xxxxxxxxxx\nShubanshu Bajaj+91\-xxxxxxxxxx</item>
		<item>The International Council of E\-Commerce Consultants (EC\-Council) is a member\-based organization that certifies individuals in various e\-business and information security skills. It is the owner and creator of the world famous Certified Ethical Hacker (CEH), Computer Hacking Forensics Investigator (CHFI) and EC\-Council Certified Security Analyst (ECSA)/License Penetration Tester (LPT) programs, and as well as many others programs. Its objective is to raise international awareness towards increased education and ethics in IT Security. The EC\-Council is known primarily as a professional certification body.\nThe International Council of  E\-Commerce Consultants (EC\-Council) presents a 2 day workshop on Mobile Hacking, Cyber Forensics and Penetration Testing. During the two day (8 hours each day) training of Mobile Hacking, Cyber Forensics and Penetration Testing Workshop the participants will learn Latest Hacking Techniques and Tools through PowerPoint Presentations, Live Demos and Hacking Tutorials with HD Videos.\n\nThe fee is Rs. 1000\/\- per student.\n\nTakeaway\n1.Toolkit (Hacking Tools + Backtrack) will be provided to each participant.\n2. Participation certificate from IIT Indore and TechBharat Consulting.\n\nFor Details, Contact:\nShikhar Bansal+91\-xxxxxxxxxx\nVinit Sharaswat+91\-xxxxxxxxxx xxx@xmail.com</item>
        <item>\"India’s First and Unique Formula Based High Performance Car Training Programme\"\nThe most modern technologies are the derivatives of fundamentals of engineering, basic physics, chemistry and mathematics. To make the students understand this fact so that they could understand and appreciate the theories they learn in their classes, we have chosen \"a high performance vehicle to design in a formula based style\" as there is a huge learning of optimization of Speed, Strength and Stability simultaneously which undoubtedly is an exceptional design challenge to take.\n\nA full time Training Program on \"Automotive System design and development\" specially targeted on Formula1 Car Design and Development with comprehensive theory and design, providing advanced learning of Automobile designing and manufacturing is being presented. \n\nCOURSE DURATION: 30 Hrs. (20 Hrs. + 10 Hrs.) \nCOURSE CHARGES: Rs 4000 per head.\nDates: 1st\-6th Feb\nVenue: IIT INDORE\n\nHighlights:\n1. Certification in association with Fluxus’14, IIT Indore.\n2. I week Crash Course on \"Automotive System design and development\".\n3. Get your hands dirty with designing tools e.g. Solidworks, Ansys etc.\n4. Learn all concept of Vehicle dynamics w.r.t. Formula 1. \n5. Get guidance from experts for different competitions e.g. Supra , Baja etc. \n6. Free*Accommodation @ IIT INDORE for a Week\n7. Get a chance to participate in the various competitions lined\-up just after the Workshop.\n8. Be a part of Central India’s Biggest College Fest\-Fluxus’14\nHurry Up!! Limited Seats Only!!\n\nFor further Details, Contact:\nShantanu Rajput    +91 xxxxxxxxxx\nVineet Kataria  +91 xxxxxxxxxx\n\n*conditions apply</item>
        <item>\"Workshop on Android App Development followed by Pre\-limes round for AADC Event\"\nVISIT http://www.aadc.in/\n\nAADC Highlights:\n* AADC is a National Level Competition on Android Application Development\n* 1st time in India a competition on Android App Development\n* Competition will be held in 30 different centers across India among 4500+ students.\n* The final round of AADC will held at Fluxus 2014 – IIT Indore on 7th – 9th Feb 2014.\n* Prizes up to Rs 1,00,000/\- to be won which includes Android Mobiles/Tablets etc,\n\nDates:\n25\-26th Jan\nVenue:\nIIT Indore\nFees:\n1000/\- Rs per participant\n\nFor further details, Contact:\nShikhar Bansal: +91\-xxxxxxxxxx\nRadhe: +91\-xxxxxxxxxx</item>
	</string-array>
    <string-array id="quizEventsAbst" name="quizEventsAbst">
        <item>\"Man will not live without answers to his questions.\" says Hans.J.Morgenthau.\nWe at Quiz Fest, Fluxus\'14 play host to this unfaltering desire you have, to conquer questions. How? By granting you the opportunity to pit your wit against the Quiz Master.\nQuizzes have always been the best way to keep up with the amount of information soaring in from around the world. And if Quizzes like these caption you to be the Quiz\-Wizards of Central India\'s Largest Techno\-Cult Fest, you are surely in for it, aren\'t you?\nSo tighten your seat belts, pump your fists, get ready for some nerve wracking and unsettling of hair as quizzes from variant genres are waiting to arrive at your stations!!\n\n\nCome on, now! Be the man Hans.J.Morgenthau thinks you are :P\n\n\-Ramesh Krishna +91xxxxxxxxxx</item>
        <item>\"We wish you first, a sense of logic\nOnly those who know illusion and love it, will go far.\nOtherwise you spend your lives in confusion...\nOf what you think they are stating, to what they really are!!\"\n\n\nObscura\-IQ Quiz is the foremost event of The Quiz Fest that needs you to put your wits in the nifty world of logic. This event swirls you\nthrough exciting rounds of Einstein Riddles, Murder mysteries, Logical Thinking\nand much more to test your logical and deductive skills.\nThe best thing about Obscura is that, for its namesake, it puts only your quotient of intelligence to test. Common Sense is all what you need! What we wished you first)\nSo,\nCome. Go far. Win it!\n\nSurya Teja Thogaru    +91xxxxxxxxxx xxx@xmail.com\nJaswanth Singh    +91xxxxxxxxxx\nRajesh Verma +91xxxxxxxxxx</item>
        <item>Ever wondered what shooting stars were? Or, what is it that turned the sky blue?\nDid it ever strike you to know the reason behind \'em?\nIf you have preserved this curious child in you, who questions almost everything he does not know the reason for, you are just at the right place!\nEureka is Quiz Club\'s move to make you quench your Archimedian thirst!\nSo, bring in with your aura, the Eureka factor...\n\n\- N.S.Vidyaranya +91xxxxxxxxxx\n\- Abhinav Marda +91xxxxxxxxxx</item>
        <item>Welcome to The Colosseum\- where Sports and Entertainment collide in a profusion of blood and sweat\nThe year is 90 AD. All the stands are filled. The crowd is excited. The tension in the air is palpable. Caesar and the Pretoria are lounging in their boxes. The rich adjust their feather cushions. The poor haggle spiritedly over bets.\nThe people are happy.\nThe Colosseum is an arena for the knowledgeable folks of the world. Do you have what it takes to escape devious traps set for sports? Do you have what it takes to parry questions about entertainment? DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO WIN THE APPROVAL OF THE CROWD?\n\n\- Mayur Joseph Bency +91xxxxxxxxxx\n\- Rishabh Chaudhary +91xxxxxxxxxx</item>
        <item>\"The more you learn, the more you realize how little you know..\" – Socrates\nThink you know about a thing or two? You dare challenge the machine?\nGet ready to be baffled and bombarded with questions about everything under the sun. Not for the faint\-hearted, \'Quizooka\' will test your knowledge; in a manner like no other... delving into trivia you never knew... a lot of times about things you thought you knew (as a worthy challenger).\nThe last 3 teams standing would deservedly take the spoils... and boast of challenging and beating the machine \- a joy few mortals know.\nBut REMEMBER, know\-how is just the beginning; wit and clever thinking are often the machine\'s true weakness.\n\n\- Karthik Muthuraman +91xxxxxxxxxx\n\- Anas Shaikh +91xxxxxxxxxx</item>
        <item>So you think you keep yourself updated with the latest buzz of tech world???\"If you tried to read every document on the web, then for each day\'s effort, you would be a year further behind in your goal.\" So not just latest but it\'s about the whole journey of tech evolution... Do you think you\'re up to the challenge? Then wait no further! Join us to test your knowledge, and know where you stand...\n\n\-Priyan +91xxxxxxxxxx\nArvind Sagar()</item>
    </string-array>
	<string-array id="litEventsAbst" name="litEventsAbst">
		<item>Do you find charms, transfiguration and even history of magic more interesting than maths and science? Are you in a habit of trying out Accio to summon the T.V. remote before you actually go get it? Have you ever furtively picked up an odd shaped twig and muttered a charm in the hope of being accepted at Hogwarts? If yes, come check your PotterMania level by answering some of the easiest and toughest questions at the Harry Potter quiz @Fluxus \'14 informal zone.</item>
		<item>Yes, you guessed it right! Ready your wits for some word-building fun. Manoeuvre your way through a plethora of word games that would surely put your vocabularies to test. So buck up as everyone can try a shot at the right word. The contest is gonna be neck to neck, with a bagful of exciting prizes to take!</item>
		<item>Secret alert for all Patricks, Richards and Sherlocks! So you think you can crack this code? For all the code breaking enthusiasts comes an event to test their deductive skills and turn their stomachs, Cache Of Lexis(COL). There has been a disaster and its difficult to determine what is the final secret. That is where you, the Ultimate Code Breaker come up. Form a team and use your deductive/abductive/inductive skills to crack set of puzzles to reach the ultimate secret behind the coded problem and win exciting prizes</item>
		<item>This event is only for students of classes 9th and 10th.\n\n\"Lock up your libraries if you like; but there is no gate, no lock, no bolt that you can set upon the freedom of my mind.\"\nWith these words by Virginia Woolf in our minds, we present before u the most interesting, most intriguing and the most innovative specimen of literary competition\-RANSENSE.So, all the budding writers, poets and other enthusiasts, scratch your minds, let your inside speak and your quill tear the paper to create a masterpiece you have never written before. In life, we often leave it on our fate to decide the end but here is the opportunity for the zealous and creative minds to make their own story of the already begun one and mesmerize the readers with humorous bends, an eye catching climax and high vocabulary. Use your talent, accept the challenge and prove yourself of what you are worth.\nThe rules of the game are simple yet challenging\-random paragraph along the list of ten words will be given with you must continue ensuring the use of all ten words and convert it into an article, essay, story, dialogue or a poem.</item>
        <item>For both the loquacious and the reticent, JAM(Just a Minute) invites you to speak on a given topic for sixty seconds without hesitation,repition, or deviation.Share your perspectives and experiences with the world.\nSo Grab the topic, Jump on the stage and get a chance to win exciting prizes.</item>
        <item>Ever felt dyslexic over the spelling of receive? Were you ever able to recollect the \'s\'es in Mississippi? Word\-spellings come to haunt you again with this uniquely designed Spell Bee. Designed with a variety of tricky and confusing words, be ready to amaze or be amazed! Brace yourself for the challenge, can you get them all?</item>
        <item>Is it true that money rules over us all? And if not, why are more and more engineers opting for business studies over further studies in their own field just because it would land them a job that pays better? If you have an opinion and are able and willing to defend it and take it home, the debate at Fluxus \'14 is just the thing for you. Put forward your views. Be fierce. Be relentless. Be convincing. And get a chance to win exciting prizes.</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>